# ARAWN DAVIES

Address · Phone

Arawn.davies780@gmail.com · www.linkedin.com/in/arawn-davies· www.arawn-davies.co.uk

An efficient communicator and able to work in a team as both a leader and a team member, with extensive experience in many IT roles. Coming from a multilingual and multinational family of Welsh and Indian descent, I have acquired experience at helping people who speak English as a second language in aiding them with their problems and needs. I am an ambitious, highly motivated, and intelligent young man who takes pride in delivering work to the best of my ability. With a kind, friendly and approachable personality, I take pride in providing excellent support to people. Highly proficient worker with 10 years using a vast range of different programming languages, software suites and hardware equipment, I can easily adapt and become familiar with any new platform used in my work.

#### **SKILLS**

- Highly skilled in a wide range of different programming languages and architectures
- Full UK Driving License, held for 3 years
- A lot of experience in using Linux, Git, virtualization, LAMP, UNIX and software architecture
- Highly experienced in IT, electronics, and IT tutoring
- Fluent in English
- Experienced in languages C/C++, C#, Java, JavaScript, HTML, PHP, Assembly, and .NET.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

AUG 2021 - SEPT 2021

## **CUSTOMER SUPPORT SPECIALIST, COMMUNITY BRANDS UK**

Providing customer support for several MIS platforms to hundreds of schools across the UK, triaging issues with engineers and helping prioritize urgent cases.

JUNE 2015 - OCT 2021

# **DIRECTOR, ADX TECHNOLOGIES**

Provider of specialist technical support for many different platforms and other personal computing devices and networks

MAY 2019 - AUG 2019

# **ELECTRICIAN + ENGINEERING WORKER, FREELANCE**

Worked in the local community in Harlech, North Wales. I helped outdoor structures and installed light fixtures, wall sockets, telecommunications and other IT technical support for different customers.

#### **EDUCATION**

SEP 2014 - JUL 2016

**GCSES, WIGSTON COLLEGE** 

Certificate in Digital Applications (CiDA) B Electronics, Maths & Music B Double Science B/C

SEP 2016 – JUN 2017

**GCSES, REGENT COLLEGE** 

ICT Distinction Star English A\*/B Business Studies B Psychology C

#### FURTHER EDUCATION

**SEP 2017 – JUN 2019** 

#### A LEVELS, WYGGESTON QUEEN ELIZABETH I COLLEGE

BTEC Level 3 Extended Diploma, Distinction-Distinction-Merit Equivalent of 3 A-levels at AAB

**OCT 2020 - PRESENT** 

## **BACHELOR OF SCIENCE DEGREE, DE MONTFORT UNIVERSITY**

Computer Science BSc. 4 years with a placement

#### **ACTIVITIES**

JAN 2021 – MAR 2020

# **VOLUNTEER, LOROS SPIRAL SCRATCH**

I volunteered at the local LOROS Hospice music charity store in Leicester, I authorized sales, aided in organization of donations, stock, listing and serving customers with any questions they may have.

SEP 2016 - PRESENT

#### **AUDIO ENGINEER. FREELANCE**

As a multi-instrumentalist, I combine my extensive IT software and hardware skills in addition to my music knowledge to provide digital audio workstation, computer & music audio equipment services to several local customers.

## **PROJECTS**

#### FOUNDER/MAINTAINER, MEDLI OPERATING SYSTEM

For almost a decade, I have been developing an operating system in my spare time for PCs in C# and .NET. This has been a major project of mine as it has aided in my learning and practical use of skills which I have learned over my career and education history. This can be seen at <a href="https://www.github.com/Siarantie-Solutions/Medli">www.github.com/Siarantie-Solutions/Medli</a>

## CORE TEAM MEMBER, COSMOS (C# OPEN-SOURCE MANAGED OPERATING SYSTEM)

In addition to working on my operating system Medli, I have been working alongside a group of other highly experienced developers to develop a toolkit for other developers to create full fledged operating systems using existing applications and source code. This can be seen at www.github.com/CosmosOS/Cosmos

# **FOUNDER, SIARANITE SOLUTIONS**

As an umbrella organization that manages Medli, I also use this organization to manage my other software projects that I have developed and created over the years. These include assembler byte-code virtual machines for embedded devices, compiler deployment scripts, and file systems for storing and managing data on storage devices. You can see a list of these projects <a href="https://www.github.com/Siaranite-Solutions">www.github.com/Siaranite-Solutions</a>